webmasterserve.com 2017-10-20

# Privacy | WebmasterServe Forums

____

### Welcome to WebmasterServe!

FREE TO JOIN! Join us now to engage in informative and friendly discussions about Webmastering, SEO, SEM, Internet Marketing, Programming, Graphic Design, Online Jobs and more. What are you waiting for? Ready to join our friendly community? It takes just one minute to register.

### WebmasterServe Cookies and Privacy Policy

This page discusses your privacy concerns due to usage of WebMasterServe including how cookies are used by WMS. If you continue to use WMS, you are consenting to our Use of Cookies, our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

### Payment Information and Transactions

WMS uses third-party payment processors including but not limited to PayPal for various transactions on WMS. Payment information is NOT stored on WMS except payment transaction numbers, payee and payer email addresses and shipping addresses when applicable and relevant payment details which DOES NOT include any passwords, credit card numbers, bank information, etc.

Please refer to our Terms of Use for other aspects of our policy which relates to your privacy and your content.

### Your Information used by WMS

Just like any other large website online, WMS logs into our database your IP address and geographic information, including your email address used for registering on WMS and personal information you provided.

We use your location and other personal data to enhance the website services by providing you with content and features best suited for your profile. Your personal information maybe used in collaboration with third-parties to serve relevant advertising or content. All breach of conduct by third parties is solely the liability of the third parties in question.

We shall NEVER rent, lease, sell or use your email addresses or any personal information to third parties. We use your content information to provide you with updates, notifications and keep you informed about the latest conent suitable for your purposes. Users have option to opt-out of such site mailings using their Preferences section.

### Your Account and Content

Users are only allowed to create and maintain one account in their lifetime. Accounts are held by individuals and not companies they are associated with, hence accounts are NOT subject to transfers. Accounts may not be bought and sold or given away to other parties. Such accounts are subject to immediate termination.

WebMasterServe is a public forum, hence the content your post or upload on WMS is public and shall remain the same. The simple rule is, do not post anything here which you do not want the world to know. All posted content maybe used, reused, quoted and published by WMS without prior consent. You still own copyright to your content.

You may be able to delete the content you posted provided you have the required User Rank to be eligible for such action. If you are unable to delete your content and would like it deleted, please use the Support Ticket section to open a support ticket with details about the content, URL and the reason you would like the content to be deleted from WMS. WMS reserves the right to edit, modify, delete or retain the content.

### What Cookies Are

Cookies are small files stored on your computer by your web browser (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox) at the request of a site you're viewing. This allows the site you're viewing to remember things about you, such as your preferences and history or to keep you logged in.

Cookies may be stored on your computer for a short time (such as only while your browser is open) or for an extended period of time, even years. Cookies not set by this site will not be accessible to us.

### Our Cookie Usage

WebmasterServe uses cookies for numerous things, including:

  * Registration and maintaining your preferences. This includes ensuring that you can stay logged in and keeping the site in the language or appearance that you requested.
  * Analytics. This allows us to determine how people are using the site and improve it.
  * Advertising cookies (possibly third-party). If this site displays advertising, cookies may be set by the advertisers to determine who has viewed an ad or similar things. These cookies may be set by third parties, in which case this site has no ability to read or write these cookies.
  * Other third-party cookies for things like Facebook or Twitter sharing. These cookies will generally be set by the third-party independently, so this site will have no ability to access them.

### Removing/Disabling Cookies

Managing your cookies and cookie preferences must be done from within your browser's options/preferences. Here is a list of guides on how to do this for popular browser software:
